[
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Which ones of those cities are biggest in population?",
        "choices": ["Paris", "Bordeaux", "Lyon", "Marseille"],
        "answer": ["Paris", "Lyon"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Technology",
        "question": "Who were the founders of the Apple company?",
        "choices": ["Bill Gates", "Steve Jobs", "Steve Wozniak", "Ronald Wayne"],
        "answer": ["Steve Jobs", "Steve Wozniak", "Ronald Wayne"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Colors",
        "question": "What colors can you find in a rainbow",
        "choices": ["Red", "Blue", "Pink", "Indigo"],
        "answer": ["Red", "Blue", "Indigo"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sport",
        "question": "Wich ones of those countries won more than 3 FIFA world cups?",
        "choices": ["France", "Germany", "Uruguay", "Italy"],
        "answer": ["Germany", "Italy"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Language",
        "question": "Which are the top 3 of most spoken languages in the world?",
        "choices": ["Spanish", "English", "Madarin Chinese", "Hindustani"],
        "answer": ["English", "Madarin Chinese", "Hindustani"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Which ones of those countries has white color on their flag?",
        "choices": ["Germany", "Spain", "Greece", "Norway"],
        "answer": ["Greece", "Norway"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "question": "Wich ones of those animals are mammals?",
        "choices": ["Whale", "Lion", "Snake", "Kameleon"],
        "answer": ["Whale","Lion"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "question": "Which ones of those countries have nuclear weapons?",
        "choices": ["France", "North Korea", "India", "Pakistan"],
        "answer": ["France", "North Korea", "India", "Pakistan"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Pop Culture",
        "question": "Which ones of those are Pokemons?",
        "choices": ["Caterpie", "Suricate", "Rattata", "Raticate"],
        "answer": ["Caterpie", "Rattata", "Raticate"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Religion",
        "question": "Which ones of those are sins according to the Catholic Church?",
        "choices": ["Greed", "Lust", "Jalousy", "Anger"],
        "answer": ["Greed", "Lust"]
    }
]
